let questions = [
    {
        Number: 1,
        question: "Who invented JavaScript?",
        answer: "Brendan Eich",
        options: [
            "Douglas Crockford",
            "Sheryl Sandberg",
            "Brendan Eich",
            "Steve Wozniak"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 2,
        question: "What was the first computer that had a colour display?",
        answer: "Apple II",
        options: [
            "iMac",
            "Apple II",
            "BBC Micro",
            "Amiga 500"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 3,
        question: "What percentage of people are said to plug their USB devices incorrectly during their first attempt?",
        answer: "86%",
        options: [
            "86%",
            "Must be 100%",
            "41%",
            "I assume eveyone is just like me, so 0%"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 4,
        question: "Which company first developed the Java programming language?",
        answer: "Sun Microsystems",
        options: [
            "Microsoft",
            "Google",
            "Sun Microsystems",
            "IBM"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 5,
        question: "What do you call a computer's main circuit board?",
        answer: "Motherboard",
        options: [
            "Computer board",
            "Micro Board",
            "Motherboard",
            "Fatherboard"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 6,
        question: "What does I.T. stand for?",
        answer: "Information Technology",
        options: [
            "Internet Technology",
            "Information Technology",
            "Intranet Technology",
            "Important Technology"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 7,
        question: "Who created the first modern computer?",
        answer: "Charles Babbage",
        options: [
            "Steve Jobs",
            "Bill Gates",
            "Arthur C Clarke",
            "Charles Babbage"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 8,
        question: "Which one is the first search engine in internet?",
        answer: "Archie",
        options: [
            "Google",
            "Archie",
            "Altavista",
            "WAIS"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 9,
        question: "Which one is the first web browser, invented in 1990?",
        answer: "Nexus",
        options: [
            "Internet Explorer",
            "Mosaic",
            "Mozilla",
            "Nexus"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 10,
        question: "Which of the folowing programming languages is used to create programs like applets?",
        answer: "Java",
        options: [
            "COBOL",
            "C Langauge",
            "Java",
            "BASIC"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 11,
        question: "What was the first computer virus known as?",
        answer: "Creeper Virus",
        options: [
            "Rabbit",
            "Creeper Virus",
            "Elk CLoner",
            "SCA Virus"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 12,
        question: "Which one of these languages is exclusively used for artificial intelligence?",
        answer: "Prolog",
        options: [
            "C",
            "Java",
            "J2EE",
            "Prolog"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 13,
        question: "Firewall in computer is used for what?",
        answer: "Security",
        options: [
            "Security",
            "Data Transmission",
            "Authentication",
            "Monitoring"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 14,
        question: "Which of the following, is not an operating system?",
        answer: "C",
        options: [
            "DOS",
            "Mac",
            "C",
            "Linux"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 15,
        question: "How many layers are in the OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) Model?",
        answer: "7",
        options: [
            "9",
            "3",
            "7",
            "11"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 16,
        question: "Where is the headquarters of Microsoft located?",
        answer: "Washington",
        options: [
            "Texas",
            "New York",
            "California",
            "Washington"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 17,
        question: "Computer Hard Disks were first introduced in 1956 by which company?",
        answer: "IBM",
        options: [
            "Dell",
            "Microsoft",
            "Apple",
            "IBM"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 18,
        question: "A computer uses which type of number system to calculate and store data?",
        answer: "Binary",
        options: [
            "Decimal",
            "Octal",
            "Binary",
            "Hexadecimal"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 19,
        question: "In the computer world, a Trojan is referred to, as what?",
        answer: "Malware",
        options: [
            "Virus",
            "Malware",
            "Worm",
            "Spyware"
        ]
    },
    {
        Number: 20,
        question: "How many layers are in the TCP/IP protocol?",
        answer: "4",
        options: [
            "7",
            "5",
            "4",
            "11"
        ]
    }
];